Guide to the Stanford University Postcard Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Postcards (individual)
  - Mausoleum, Undated; 309; Sepia Print
  - Mausoleum, 1912; 310; Photo
    Message: The Mausoleum of the Stanfords at Stanford University, California.
    It is Easter Vacation now and I have been making some more pictures again.
    From Your brother, H.A. Holden
  - Medical Center, 1967; 311; Color Print
    Medical Center
  - Museum, 1911; 312; Photo
    Caption: Stanford University Museum
    shows flooded area in front of Museum; note on back: "Jan. 15-22, 1911. "New Lake" from storm of 'll"
    Museums.
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 313; Color Print
    Caption: 326-Memorial arch, looking west, Stanford University, California
    Memorial Arch
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 314; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 315; Sepia Print
    Caption: 5077 - Memorial Arch, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 316; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Stanford University
    Imprint: First National Bank
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 317; B/W Print
    Caption: 7284 - Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal.: Memorial Arch
    Imprint: M. Rieder for Tupman Bros.
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 318; Color Print
    Caption: 259 - Memorial Arch, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Cal.
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 319; Color Print
    Caption: 120 - Memorial Arch. Stanford University, California.
  - Memorial Arch, 1904; 320; Color Print
    Caption: 8575 - Memorial Court and Arch, Leland Stanford Jr. University
    Imprint: Detroit Photographic Co.
  - Memorial Arch, 1904; 321; Color Print
    Caption: 8574 - Memorial Court and Arch, Leland Stanford Jr. University.
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 322; Color Print
    Caption: 63 - Memorial Arch, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: Richard Behrendt
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 323; B/W Print
    appears to be published for advertising
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 324; B/W Print
    Caption: A14070 - Memorial Arch, Stanford University, Cal.
    Imprint: M. Rieder and Dresden. No. 6105
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 325; B/W Print
    Caption: 7348 - Memorial Arch, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 326; Color Print
    Caption: 259 - Memorial Arch and Court, Stanford University, California
    (on front of card) "Cecil Neal"; (on back) "Miss Marie Hatler, Chaparral School. Chaparral."
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 328; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California. - 100 feet high, 90 feet in width; to the right group of the Stanford Family.
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 329; B/W Print
    Caption: Ruins of Stanford Memorial Arch, Palo Alto destroyed by earthquake, April 18, 1906. Stanford Family monument in foreground.
    544-546 South Spring St., Los Angeles Cal
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 330; Photo
    Caption: Stanford University after Earthquake of 1906
    Memorial Arch post 1906
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 331; Color Print
    Caption: no.224 - Memorial Arch at Stanford's University, Palo Alto, California wrecked by earthquake April 18, 1906.
    Imprint: Chas. Weidner
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 332; Photo
    Imprint: A. S. Walley
    Stanford Memorial Arch post 1906
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 333; Color Print
    Caption: The Great Earthquake and Fire, San Francisco, Cal., 1906. The Memorial Arch at Leland Stanford, Jr., University, Ruined by the Earthquake
    Imprint: The American News Company
    illegibly written on back: "Hilda Feb 8 1909. Emma Hiewoehner Alpha La"
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 334; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Stanford University Destroyed by Earthquake, April 18th, 1906
  - Memorial Arch, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 335; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Arch, Stanford University, Cal., after the earthquake and fire, April 18, 1906.
  - Memorial Arch, pre 1906; 327; Photo
    Caption: Memorial Arch
    large piece of black paper is glued to the back of card.
  - Memorial Auditorium, Undated; 336; Tinted Print
    Caption: 48 - Memorial Hall. Stanford University, California
    Imprint: E. L. Hyde
    Memorial Auditorium
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 337; B/W Print
    Caption: 13 - Stanford Memorial Church, Stanford University.
    Imprint: H. W. Simkins
    Memorial Church - Pre 1906 - exterior
    Memorial Church
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 338; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 339; Color Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 340; Color Print
    Caption: 258 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
    (photo made c.1905 as changes in the mosaics on both [illegible word] sides of design were made in Oct. 1904.)"
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 341; Color Print
    Caption: 258 - Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, California.
    Message: Miira baby was born yest at. 4.oclock. a girl. Grandma is all smiles. Dad is at work here an the p. office running the hostes I guess that is what it is called. We havent heard from May yet. Mother.
    postmarked May 13 11-AM 1909 from Palo Alto, Cal. Addressed ti (?) Gestie Riekl, 1166.5 Washington St., San Francisco
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 342; Color Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 343; Color Print
    Caption: none (cut off?)
    Message: "it is perfectly grand, & I hope he takes me down sometime this year. I don't know whether I shall go there next year or not. At any rate I wont go to Mills. Julia agrees with me in this. How I wish I could go to Wellesley. It wouldn't be any more expensive than at Mills & the school is so much higher & has so much better standing, but it is so far off & so many girls apply that there would be no chance unless one applies two or three yrs. ahead the boys...(cut off from there)"
    Imprint: none (cut off?)
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 344; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church. Stanford University. Palo Alto California: This is one of the most remarkable structures of its kind and was built as a Memorial to Stanford Leland [sic], and it stands in the University Grounds one mile from Palo Alton [sic]. It is 34 miles from San Francisco.
    Imprint: Sanborn Vail & Co.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 345; Color Print
    Caption: 119 - Memorial Church. Stanford University. California
    (written on front) "This is one fo the most beautiful pieces of work in existence. Cost nearly a million." Gift of Nora Hall 1971.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 346; Color Print
    Caption: No. 119 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, California. Totally destroyed by earthquake Apr. 18, 1906.
    Message: We would like to have seen this.
    postmarked May 28 7-30A 1909 from Palo Alto, Cal. Addressed to Dr. T. M. Williams, 61 West 104th St., New York City
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 347; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 1904; 348; Color Print
    Caption: 258 - Memorial Chapel, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Cal.
    Message: (none, but this card was apparently sent: on front is written: "Johnny sent me Valantine [sic] Day - 1904.")
    Imprint: Ewdard H. Mitchell
    postmarked Feb 15 3-30P 1904 from San Francisco, Ca. Addressed to Miss Dorothy Boericke, Washington St., near Van Ness, San Francisco, Cal.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 349; B/W Print
    Caption: 7287 - Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal: After the Sunday Sermon
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 350; Photo
    Caption: The Stanford Memorial Church
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 351; Photo
    Caption: Memorial Church. Stanford University.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 352; Color Print
    Caption: 5040 - Exterior of the Memorial Church at Stanford University, California.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 353; Color Print
    Caption: 258 - Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 354; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church Stanford University, Cal. Destroyed by Earthquake, April 18, 1906.
    Imprint: I. Scheff & Bros.
    (written on back) "This building has been restored as before"
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 355; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, California.
    Message: (written on front) "The picture on the Church is the sermon on the Mount in mosaics. It was blown out by the free of air, from the tower falling into the body of the church. There will be a flat Spanish tower, as were in keeping with the style of the other buildings. We are having very light touches of frost, but we hardly know it, as the flowers are blooming right along. The weather is perfect.
    postmarked Oct 24 6PM 1906 from Stanford University, Cal. Addressed to Mrs. Colean, 1102 W. Fayette Ave., Springfield, Ill.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 356; B/W Print
    Caption: 7349 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 357; Color Print
    Caption: 5212 - Chapel, Stanford University.
    Imprint: The PCK Series
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 358; Color Print
    Caption: 626 - The Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal.
    Imprint: Britton & Rey
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 1903; 359; Color Print
    Caption: 684 - Memorial Church, Stanford University., Cal.
    Imprint: M. Rieder for Alice Hare
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 1903; 360; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University., (Masterpiece of Architecture of the Present Century.)
    Message: "Santa Clara, Cal. Oct - 2. To reduce my (unreadable word) I am offering for next five days (unreadable word) finish this card for 90 cts per 100 or 500 for $4.00. If you do not handle cards please hand to someone who does. and oblige Mrs Alice Hare Santa Clara"
    Imprint: M. Rieder for Mrs. Alice Hare
    postmarked Oct 2 6PM 1905 from Sunnyvale, Cal. Addressed to Johnson Drug Co., Sunnyvale, California
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 361; B/W Print
    Caption: 5076 - Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 362; Sepia Print
    Caption: 141 - Memorial Church Stanford University, Cal.
    (written on back) "Horace Davis estate, 1/16/58 (photo made c. late 1904 or 1905 or before April 1906) mosaics show changes made in Oct. 1904."
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 363; B/W Print
    Message: written on front: "before the earthquake our (unreadable word)"
    postmarked Apr 1907 from San Francisco. Addressed to Carleton Mathis, 2230 Maplewood Ave, Toledo, Ohio
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 364; Sepia Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Leland Stanford Jr. University
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 1946; 365; Color Print
    Caption: 3444 - Memorial Church and Quadrangle, Stanford University
    stamped May 27 1946 Stanford University Library; Memorial Church before 1906. On front, Memorial Church is pictured before and after the earthquake.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 366; Sepia Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 367; Sepia Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 368; Sepia Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 369; Color Print
    Caption: 8577 - Memorial Church, Leland Stanford Jr. University
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 381; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Church - Stanford University
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 370; Color Print
    Caption: 5214 - Chapel, Stanford University.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) pre 1906, 371; Photo
    Caption: Memorial Church. Stanford University, Cal.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 372; Color Print
    Caption: 64 - Memorial Chapel Stanford University. Cal
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 373; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, Cal.
    Imprint: H. S Crocker
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 374; Color Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 375; B/W Print
    Caption: 7283 - Memorial Church. Stanford Unviersity. Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 376; Sepia Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) pre 1906, 377; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 378; Color Print
    Caption: No. 1010 Beautiful California - Stanford Memorial Chapel
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 379; Color Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 380; Color Print
    Same as no. 379 except for small image of church after '06 quake included on front
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 382; Photo
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 1908; 383; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Memorial Church, Cal.
    Message: April 28, 1908: Spent a very pleasant day at Palo Alto, visiting Stanford Univ. W.C. and E. R. Blasdale.
    postmark: Apr. 29 6-PM 1908 from Berkeley/ Received: Ilwaco, Wash. March 12 1 PM 1908. To: Miss Annie Morse, Ilwaco, Washington
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) Pre 1906, 384; Color Print
    Imprint: Live Oak Stables
    Other caption on front: "When writing to friends use the Card. Do not fail to visit Stanford University and also take the drive. Ask for Mr. ____, Driver. Live Oak Stables, 440 High Street, Palo Alto, Cal..."
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 385; B/W Print
    Caption: Facing the Altar, Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal., after earthquake and fire, April 18, 1906.
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1907; 386; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University. Palo Alto, California. The Church, at a cost of $1,600,000 was wrecked by Earthquake of April 18, 1906.
    Message: Addressed to: Carleton Mathis, 2230 Maplewood Ave, Toledo, Ohio: "This will give you some idea of the work of the "quake" (illegible word) apr 24/07"
    postmark: apr 1907
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 387; Color Print
    Caption: 225 - Memorial Arch [sic] at Stanford's University, Palo Alto, California wrecked by earthquake April 18, 1906.
    gift of Miss Carol Day; 1-20-66; although caption describes Memorial Arch, picture on postcard is actually of church.
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 388; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University, California: Before and after the Earthquake of April 18, 1906
    Imprint: Stuart
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 389; Photo
    Imprint: A. Swalley (?)
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1907; 390; Color Print
    Caption: Exterior ruins of the Memorial Church, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal. Wrecked by the earthquake of April 18, 1906
    Message: (illegible message on front: 8 lines written in pencil)
    addressed to Miss Celestine Zetka, #27 Grafton Ave, Newark, N. J.
    postmark: Apr 22 10-AM 1907 from San Francisco, Cal.
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 391; Photo
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 392; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford Memorial Chapel, Palo Alto, after the earthquake of April 18, 1906.
  - Memorial Church, Damaged by Earthquake, 1906; 393; B/W Print
    Caption: Front View, Memorial Chapel, Stanford University, after the earthquake, April 18, 1906.
  - Memorial Church, Post Quake Design (not adopted), post 1906; 394; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal.
    Imprint: 484 - Pacific Novelty Co.
    written on back: "One design (never adopted) for rebuilding Memorial Church Tower after earthquake of 1906. This is an artist's conception. Surprising that it should be perpetuated on postcard; note plan to have 12 apostles in tower niches"
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 395; B/W Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 396; Photo
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 397; B/W Print
    Imprint: The Albertype Co./Hyde's Book Store
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 398; Color Print
    Caption: Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 399; Color Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 400; Color Print
    Caption: 5389 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 1928; 401; Color Print
    Caption: 4275 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, California.
    Message: "San Francisco, Calif: Dear Alice and All, I am having a wonderful time here in Frisco. It is a fine city but not so pretty as LA. How are you all. I hope well I have gained 10 pounds since coming to California to (illegible) will let you here from use when I get home Love to all I remaine as ever you little (illegible name)."
    adressed to: Miss Alice Doherty, 726-4-Ave, Dallas, Texas
    postmark: May 1928 from San Francisco
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 402; Color Print
    Caption: 4275 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 403; Photo
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 1947; 404; Color Print
    Caption: PA5: - Memorial Church. Stanford University. Palo Alto, California.
    Message: "11/12/47: Greetings. I'll be back with you Tuesday or Wednesday. I will telephone you when I get there -- I was to have gone to work tomorrow -- Nov-3 -- but I broke my arm instead -- so I will be seeing you. Love to all (illegible name)."
    addressed to: Mrs. C. Laddisuire, Route 25 -- Box 2, Los Gatos, Calif.
    postmark: Nov 3, 10:30 AM, 1947 from San Francisco, Calif.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 405; Color Print
    Caption: 425 - Memorial Church Thru [sic] Arcade, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif.
    Imprint: Stanley A. Plitz
    additional caption on back: "Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif. Stanford Memorial Chapel -- located on the Campus of Stanford University, is considered one of the most beautiful churches in America. The extensive use of art mosaics for mural decorations combine to make it a structure more than unique in character, worthy of visiting and well remembered."
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 406; Color Print
    Caption: 426 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California
    additional caption on back: "Memorial Church, Stanford University is considered one of the most beautiful churches in America. The extensive use of art mosaics for mural decorations combine to make it a structure more than unique in character, worhty of visiting and well remembered."
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 407; Color Print
    Caption: 603 - Memorial Church Through Arcade, Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif.
    Imprint: San Jose Chamber of Commerce
    additional caption on back: "Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif. Located on the Campus of Stanford University, founded 1887, Stanford Memorial Chapel is recognized as one of the most beautiful churches in America. Extensive use of art mosaics for mural decorations and the pictorial setting make it a structure unique in character, morthy of a vista [sic] that will be remembered."
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 1957; 408; Color Print
    Caption: 603 - Memorial Church, Through Arcade, Stanford University Palo Alto, Cailf.
    Message: "Hi! Left Lawsons at 12 & arrived at 9 pm. No trouble, beautiful trip weather nice, not to [sic] hot. Ruths place is sure nice, Called Marguerite to make a date & she has the mumps so that Trip is out. Going to Santa Cruz Sat. Saw Mary Whittaker. What a town, fraid I'd get lost if I were turned loose. Sure some beautiful homes here. Ruth has a lovely Magnolia tree in front yard. Lemon, Orang [sic], apple tree in back & grape vines all over the back fence. Will see you next week. Love 'Marie.'"
    addressed to: Mrs. Vera Pierce, Box 148, Hydesville, Calif.
    postmark: Aug 28 11:30 AM 1957 from Campbell, Calif.
    additional caption on back: "Located in the campus of Stanford University, founded 1887, Stanford Memorial Chapel is recognized as one of the most beautiful churches in America. Extensive use of art mosaics for mural decorations and the pictorial setting make it a structure unique in character, worthy of a visit that will be well remembered."
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 409; B/W Print
    Caption: The Memorial Church, Stanford University
    Imprint: Bardell Hi-Gloss Print for John M. Yanicks
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 1925; 410; B/W Print
    Caption: 254 - Memorial Church Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: "Dear Friends, Just a Christmas wish to you both for health and happiness and good cheer. Am very well myself, and quite comfortable. Have not been in Oakland since October. but expect to often at Christmas & New Year at my cousins' house. All is (illegible rest of sentence) Sincerely yours (illegibel name)."
    addressed to: Rev. & Mrs. Chas. M. Wendte, 141 Parkside Drive, Berkeley, Calif.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 411; Tinted Print
    Caption: 27 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: The Albertype Co. for Hyde's Book Store
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 412; Sepia Print
    Imprint: Bardell Art
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 413; Photo
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 1935; 414; Color Print
    Caption: 5 - Stanford Memorial Chapel, Palo Alto, California
    Message: "10-25-35: Dear Mother. Just to let you know we are both well but very busy. We are going to move Nov. 6. Have been very busy getting ready. Business is also picking up. Geo. now has several good men. Hope this finds you feeling much better, Will write soon. Our address after Nov. 6 is 1101 Green Street, Apt 404. Much love from us both, Charlotte."
    adressed to: Mrs Julia A. Martin, 105 High Street, Ellsworth, Maine
    postmark: Oct 26 1935 from San Francisco
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 415; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford Chapel, Stanford University
    Imprint: The Process Photo Studios
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 416; Color Print
    Caption: (partially removed) --Perhaps the most famous of Stanford University's landmarks is the Stanford Memorial Church. The Facade of the building is decorated with beautiful mosaics depicting The Sermon On The Mount. Mosaics and Stained-glass windows portray characters and scenes from both the Old and New Testament.
    Imprint: California Color Card; Mike Roberts Studios
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 417; Sepia Print
    Caption: Stanford Memorial Church, Palo Alto, Cal
    Main Facade of the Entrance of the Church. Copyrighted. No. 7
    Imprint: Gabriel Moulin
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 418; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford Memorial Church on the campus of Stanford University is one of the beautiful churches of America. It's facade of colored mosaic, picturing Christ's Sermon on the Mount, was prepared in Italy.
    Imprint: Union Oil Company
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 419; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford Chapel, Palo Alto, California: World-famous for its mosaic work is this beautiful chapel on the grounds of the Stanford University. The university was founded by Senator and Mrs. Leland Stanford in memory of their son and opened in 1891.
    Imprint: Mike Roberts/M. J. Kilbane Distributing Corp.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 420; B/W Print
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 421; B/W Print
    Caption: 204 - Memorial Church, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Memorial Church (Exterior) post 1906, 422; Color Print
    Caption: 204 - Memorial Church. Stanford University Cal.